

A Director of Advertising with 10+ years of experience specializing in marketing strategy, brand messaging, and digital marketing. A strong history of building and leading diverse marketing teams to deliver integrated advertising campaigns and drive brand growth.

123 Santa Maria, San Francisco, CA 12345 ya I i ngzhang@exam p le.com (123)456-7890

# **Professional Experience**

#### Director of Advertising

Project Management Software Inc., San Francisco, CA | October 2016 - Present

- Develop advertising and digital marketing strategy for an innovative project management software solution, manage Google Ad campaigns, and secure a strategic partnership with PMI to advertise service offerings, resultingin a 150% increase in lead generation
- Lead a marketing team of 20+ personnel to improve web page, SEO, and social media performance, resultingin a 200% increase in web traffic
- Perform analysis of competitors and consumer demographics to align brand messaging across digital platforms and drive market penetration across untapped verticals

## **Advertising Specialist**

Bay Area Marketing Consultants, San Francisco, CA | May 2011 - October 2016

- Analyzed and redefined digital marketing strategy for client businesses, which included identifying opportunities to improve social media presence and paid search ads
- Provided recommendations to client stakeholders based on consumer data and industry trends and led rebranding efforts to improve sales for underperforming products

#### Education

Bachelor of Science (B,S.) Marketing University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA September 2007 - May 2011

## Key Skills

- Advertising
- ♦ Digital Marketing
- ♦ Googl e Ad Cam pa igns
- Data Analytics
- Brand Messaging